{
    "quiz": "Dr. Howard Thurman Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What is Howard Thurman known for?",
            "options": [
                "Theologian",
                "Author and Educator",
                "Civil Rights Leader",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "answer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is Howard Thurman’s Childhood Home?",
            "options": [
                "Atlanta, Georgia",
                "Jacksonville, Florida",
                "Daytona Beach, Florida",
                "San Francisco, California"
            ],
            "answer": "Daytona Beach, Florida"
        },
        {
            "question": "What Elementary School did Howard Thurman Attend?",
            "options": [
                "Bonner Elementary",
                "Turie T. Small Elementary",
                "Florida Baptist Academy in Jacksonville",
                "Daytona Colored School"
            ],
            "answer": "Florida Baptist Academy in Jacksonville"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did Howard Thurman attend high school?",
            "options": [
                "Florida Baptist Academy",
                "Excelsior High School",
                "William Raines High School",
                "Stanton High School"
            ],
            "answer": "Florida Baptist Academy"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which College did Howard Thurman attend after high school?",
            "options": [
                "Morehouse College",
                "Howard University",
                "Haverford College",
                "Colgate Rochester Theological Seminary"
            ],
            "answer": "Morehouse College"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where did Howard Thurman study philosophy?",
            "options": [
                "Boston University",
                "Haverford College",
                "Howard University",
                "Morehouse College"
            ],
            "answer": "Haverford College"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who mentored Howard Thurman?",
            "options": [
                "Mary McCleod Bethune",
                "Mahatma Gandhi",
                "Rufus Jones",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "answer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who did Howard Thurman mentor?",
            "options": [
                "Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.",
                "John Lewis",
                "Jefferson Rogers",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "answer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the interdenominational church Howard Thurman pastored?",
            "options": [
                "Mt. Zion A.M.E. church",
                "Mt. Bethel Baptist Church",
                "Church for the Fellowship of All Peoples",
                "Calvary"
            ],
            "answer": "Church for the Fellowship of All Peoples"
        },
        {
            "question": "Howard Thurman’s grandmother was a former slave who influenced him greatly. What was her name?",
            "options": [
                "Nancy Ambrose",
                "Mary Thurman",
                "Alice Jones",
                "Sue Bailey"
            ],
            "answer": "Nancy Ambrose"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Howard Thurman’s wife?",
            "options": [
                "Alice Jones Thurman",
                "Sue Bailey Thurman",
                "Mary Thurman",
                "Nancy Ambrose"
            ],
            "answer": "Sue Bailey Thurman"
        },
        {
            "question": "What time period did Howard Thurman live?",
            "options": [
                "1869 - 1950",
                "1850 - 1921",
                "1899 - 1981",
                "1889 - 1931"
            ],
            "answer": "1899 - 1981"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which school did Howard Thurman graduate from as valedictorian?",
            "options": [
                "Daytona Colored School",
                "Florida Baptist Academy",
                "Morehouse College",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "answer": "Morehouse College"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which University did Howard Thurman’s educational contributions propel him to be recognized as a historical figure enabling his childhood home to be preserved as a historical marker on the federal and Florida state registry?",
            "options": [
                "Howard University",
                "Boston University",
                "Morehouse College",
                "Bethune Cookman University"
            ],
            "answer": "Boston University"
        },
        {
            "question": "What street is his childhood home located on in Daytona Beach, Florida?",
            "options": [
                "Campbell Street",
                "Cedar Street",
                "Whitehall Street",
                "South Street"
            ],
            "answer": "Whitehall Street"
        },
        {
            "question": "When was his childhood home built?",
            "options": [
                "1790’s",
                "1850’s",
                "1890’s",
                "1920’s"
            ],
            "answer": "1890’s"
        }
    ]
}
